housecleaningcentral.com 2018-11-28

# Mrs Clean Privacy Policy-Mrs Clean

We are pleased you are interested in visiting our website. We respect your privacy and it is protected with us. This Privacy Policy explains how we process your personal information when you visit our website.

We will not sell, rent, release, or otherwise disseminate your personal information without your permission. You may visit Mrs Clean without revealing any personal information about yourself.

Personal information is required for registration in the cleaning forum. Registration is not required to view any pages on our website.

Mrs Clean uses statistical tracking software to provide metrics of site visitors and page views. The software may use cookies to track user navigation of the site for summary reporting only.

## Contact Information:

You may contact us by e-mail via the contact us page, emailing us at [info@housecleaningcentral.com](mailto:info@housecleaningcentral.com), by telephone at 425-881-8411, or by postal mail at the following location:

Corsco, Inc (DBA Mrs. Clean, Inc.)

PO Box 12001,  
Mill Creek, WA. 98082  
USA.

## Dispute Resolution

Disputes will be handled by our customer service representative. Our customer service department will promptly correct any errors.

## Data Collection

Personal information (name, address, email, phone, home specs) is required if you request an online house cleaning estimate. Other than using this information to verify your service area and review your home specs to provide an accurate cleaning estimate, this data is discarded and not used by us further in any way.

Persons who supply their phone number on-line to request a cleaning quote will only receive telephone or email contact from us regarding clarification for house cleaning or scheduling of services they have placed on-line.

Personal information is required to post information (name, email) in the house cleaning forum.

Mrs. Clean uses statistical tracking software for analysis of site volume. This software may use cookies to track user navigation for summary reporting only. We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as automatic forum logon.

We collect, (but do not use further) the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations, name and address, telephone number, payment information (e.g., credit card number and billing address).

The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our web site.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site , ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line.

## Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

## Ad Servers

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with selected companies that we allow to place ads on our web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of:

  * [Amazon privacy policy](http://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496).
  * [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

## Security

With respect to security: When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server and will notify visitors through a pop-up screen on our site, We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information [including proprietary information] that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by e-mail, calling or mailing us at the above addresses.

Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number, The DMA's Committee on Ethical Business Practices at [mgoldberger@the-dma.org](mailto:mgoldberger@the-dma.org), state or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau, state or local consumer protection office.
